<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alan LeVar Law</string>
    <string name="call_alan_button">Call Alan</string>
    <string name="do_i_need_a_lawyer_button">Do I Need A Lawyer?</string>
    <string name="my_case_button">My Case</string>
    <string name="copyright_text">"© 2021 The Law Offices of Alan LeVar "</string>
    <string name="levar_logo_description">LeVar Logo</string>
    <string name="free_case_review_button">Free Case Review</string>
    <string name="do_i_need_a_lawyer_text">Welcome to The Law Offices of Alan LeVar. Alan is an Arkansas personal injury lawyer, in practice for over 20 years. He helps innocent people who are victimized by the negligence and misconduct of others.
Alan and his team understand the difficulty in the days and weeks following a serious injury. \n \n&#xA;
        The personal injury lawyer who represents you should be someone you know will fight for you, and you can rely on while you recover from your injury.
At The Law Offices of Alan LeVar, you will get a personal injury lawyer with years of experience in auto accidents and other personal injury cases. You will also find a compassionate attorney who is more concerned with your well-being than their profit margins. \n \n&#xA;
Alan prides himself on the clear, open communication he maintains with all of his clients. He places great value on the client relationship he is able to build with each client as an individual. At The Law Offices of Alan LeVar, we represent the injured individual, never the insurance company. Our goal is to help get you the compensation you deserve to move forward with your life. \n \n&#xA;
If you live in the state of Arkansas and you need an experienced personal injury lawyer, please call The Law Offices of Alan LeVar at today for a free consultation.
In addition to auto accidents, our team is also capable of handling personal injury cases involving: \n \n&#xA;
•	Truck accidents \n&#xA;
•	Motorcycle accidents \n&#xA;
•	Construction site accidents \n&#xA;
•	Amusement park/rollercoaster accidents \n&#xA;
•	Dog bites \n&#xA;
•	Wrongful death cases \n \n &#xA; &#xA;
If you or a loved one are an Arkansas, resident, and were hurt in an accident caused by the negligence, recklessness, or intentional misconduct of another, one of our personal injury lawyers can help. Please contact The Law Offices of Alan LeVar today for a free consultation.
</string>
    <string name="pain_journal_button">Pain Journal</string>
    <string name="send_photo_button">Requested Photos</string>
    <string name="quote">This app is to provide reassurance to those that are in the middle of a law suit, as well as remind people
    that they need to be journaling daily</string>
    <string name="pain_journal_prompt">The more descriptive you can be, the better we can help.</string>
    <string name="send_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="add_photo_button">Add Photo of Injury</string>
    <string name="spinner_prefix">My Case Type: </string>
    <string name="upload_button">Upload</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="text_a_photo">Text a Photo to Alan</string>
    <string name="requested_photos_sent_photos_label">Below are the photos you have already included:</string>

</resources>